(Leonard:)- I'm Leonard, this is Raj.
- Nice to meet you.
(Alex:)I'm so excited to be working with...
(Sheldon:)Please reserve chitchat for your breaks,
Ms. Jensen.
And FYI, there'll be no breaks.
(Alex:)I should probably get to work.
(Leonard:)She seems nice.
(Raj:)Hey, you already got a girlfriend.
I call dibs.
- All I said was "She seems nice."
- Yeah, well, I love her.
(Bernadette:)Hey, I wasn't expecting
to hear from you today.
(Bernadette:)- Everything okay?
- Uh, no, not really.
(Bernadette:)What's wrong?
(Howard:)Well, remember the Soyuz capsule
they were sending to bring us home?
- Uh-huh.
- It's delayed.
(Howard:)We're gonna be here
at least another week, maybe 10 days.
(Howard:)It's the Russians, so you don't know.
They left dogs up here in the '60s.